Finally, the last form of the day.
Welcome to Stampytown, population five.
And now for the finishing touch.
The cycle of bureaucracy.
Sweet gorilla of Manila!
A letter from the Central Bureaucracy.
"Attention, Hermes Conrad.
"You are about to receive a letter
from the Central Bureaucracy."
My God! It's from the Central Bureaucracy!
I'm having a poker game tonight with
some friends from my old cryogenics job.
You guys interested?
I don't know. I only gamble with chumps.
- I'll play.
- I'm in!
Leela, Fry, Robot.
No matter what it is you're doing tonight,
I'm available.
We're playing poker.
But I'm warning you
my friends are serious players.
Bah! Big shots.
I say let the dice do the talking.
Wow, you look happy. Is someone fired?
Better. The Central Bureaucracy
is conducting an inspection tomorrow.
I will finally be promoted to Grade 35,
the 35th highest Grade there is.
Hermes, wait. We're having a poker party.
Stay and whip off
a batch of your famous jerk dip.
Sorry. I spent all day
putting my office in order.
Now I got to go home
and relax the traditional Jamaican way.
A glass of warm milk
and a good night's sleep.
Jamaican? I thought you were
some kind of outer space potato man.
Ah, that must be my old boss.
- Hello, Leela. You're fired.
- I know.
I'm sorry, but it's just that you're over
a year late for work at this point.
Let the games begin!
So I told Leela, "Your request for a date
is most flattering, but I must decline.
"These office romances never work out.
"After all, that is how
I met my horrible wife."
That's a good one.
But you never wore your ring.
I didn't know you had a wife.
And my wife doesn't know I have a job.
I keep my personal
and professional life separate.
Come on, let's deal.
You'll have plenty of time
to talk when you're poor.
What's with the specs, Bender?
They're my lucky shades.
I stole them off some lucky guy
while his lucky seeing eye dog
was taking a whiz.
Huh?
Hey!
I can't spell anything with these cards.
Finally, I have a good claw. See?
Three human females, a number
and a king giving himself brain surgery.
It doesn't matter
how many human females you have.
Bender's on a hot streak.
Eh, what can I say?
Must be my lucky shades.
Nothing. Nothing.
Crap. Crap. Garbage.
Read 'em and leak saltwater.
My baby's milk money!
I am broke.
What will I tell my horrible wife?
If I were you I'd be more worried
about that tapeworm
going to town on your intestines.
Let me see those glasses.
Um... ah...
Oh, my various gods, X-ray specs!
Guys, I swear those are prescription.
I need them for reading stuff...
On the other side of stuff.
- You cheater.
- Break his neck!
No, don't hurt him. He's my best friend.
Hey, you wouldn't hit a guy
with X-ray glasses, would you?
Easy on the arm!
Oh, my ass!
Ow!
Great cow of Moscow!
Uh... it was ghosts. Big ones.
And a tornado.
I'll never pass inspection now.
They'll bust me lower than a limbo stick
at carnival time.
And that's as low as limbo sticks get.
Aw, hey, come on, don't worry.
We'll watch you clean up.
It's too late.
The inspector will be here
in exactly one second.
Who the hell are you?
Morgan Proctor, Bureaucrat, Grade 19.
Hermes Conrad, Bureaucrat, Grade 36.
Enough friendly banter.
Shall we begin the inspection?
This way, please.
Hermes, you seem awfully calm about this.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
I'm going to jump!
No! No!
Do a flip!
Don't do it, Hermes!
You have so much to live for!
I get it. Reverse psychology.
Please, old friend, don't jump.
Use another method
that won't damage your liver.
Other people need it, you know.
Husband, no!
Out of my way, wife!
I wasn't cut out to be
a bureaucrat anyway.
I'm only anal 78.36% of the time.
I'm not worthy to stamp a form
so I'll stamp the pavement
with my flabby body.
Bureaucrat Conrad,
if you complete your death transaction
without filing a suicide
and/or falling accident permit
you will be posthumously demoted.
Life, death...
Either way I'm demoted to a tiny cubicle.
Sweet something of someplace.
As your superior,
I hereby relieve you of duty.
Consider yourself on paid vacation.
The ultimate penalty.
I recommend the health cure
on Spa 5, the sauna planet.
- Here, read.
- Spa 5? Is it good?
Oh, it's wonderful.
I don't know anything about it,
but they give me a bucket of krill
for every patient I send.
Naturally, I'll have to assign
a bureaucrat to fill in for Hermes
while he's away.
I assign me. I accept. Welcome aboard.
Then it's settled. Hermes will relax
and Zoidberg will eat. Hurrah!
I've been reviewing
your corporate records.
Regarding last Monday's delivery,
why did it take
twice as long as scheduled?
Fry got his head stuck in a crater.
I thought it would fit.
And during this period of head-crater
interaction, what were you doing?
Martini drinking contest
with the autopilot.
I would have had him this time,
but we ran out of olives.
I can explain.
You really think you can explain
how you left port
without a full complement of olives?
I think not.
- What is this, high school?
- Locker check.
Why isn't this jacket
in alphabetical order?
- What?
- The zipper.
It should be at the bottom.
Hey, sometimes a guy gets lonely.
I've never seen anything like this.
- Why is there yogurt in this cap?
- I can explain that.
See, it used to be milk, and, well,
time makes fools of us all.
You are all dismissed.
Fry, I will speak to you alone.
Uh, wait. This is the other Fry's locker.
I'm Fry with a P-H.
Admit it, Fry, you're a slob.
Mmm.
A dirty, filthy slob.
Dirty boy! Dirty, dirty, dirty!
What the hell's going on?
I thought you were anti-dirty,
not pro-dirty.
I'm surrounded by neat freaks every day.
There's nothing kinkier to me
than a filthy slop jock like you.
Oh, stop.
Now listen, you filthy pig,
no one can know about us.
- If anyone asks, I'll deny it.
- Just like every other girl I've dated.
And two, and three, and four,
and, come on, work those arms.
This is no spa. It's a forced labor camp.
Curse that Dr. Zoidberg.
If I get out of here,
he'll be looking down
the business end of a shrimp fork.
Give him one for me, too, mate.
I don't know why I go to him.
I don't miss twice, campers.
And for those six and a half reasons
I am demoting Leela to copilot.
"Copilot"? Under who?
- The autopilot.
- That drunk?
Mr. Bender, you are now
in charge of coordinating
the professor's bodily functions.
- Ahh!
- That's a full-time job.
And, Fry, as for you,
I am promoting you
to executive delivery boy.
You will no longer go on deliveries
and you will have
your own office next to mine.
All right!
Mr. Bender, would you high-five him
so that we can continue this meeting?
And on the rebound?
Ow!
Meeting adjourned.
I can't figure out
why she's so nice to you, Fry.
She's a hateful monster, this Morgan.
She scolded and hit me.
I tell you, she's risking
my friendship with her.
Bender! What happened to you?
Morgan made me walk the professor.
There we were in the park when suddenly,
some old lady says I stole her purse.
I chucked the professor at her
but she kept coming, so I had to hit her
with this purse I found.
The point is, it's Morgan's fault.
That pencil-pushing scaz-wag.
Why, if she were here, I'd...
Is she behind me?
No, I'm in front of you.
Morgan? It's 3:00 a.m.
I know. A skunk knocked over my garbage
and suddenly,
all I could think of was you.
My God. It's so repulsive.
So, this is where you eat?
Eat and sleep.
Oh, Fry!
Uh, wait! Bender's my roommate.
He could be back any second.
Not likely. I ordered him to flush out
the professor's ear wax.
Hey, Fry, I made you a candle with...
What the...
Oh, now I see. Now I get it.
Now the pieces are falling into place.
The office, the promotion,
that dwarf in my book club
who steals my opinions.
It's all coming together now.
I must say this opens my eyes.
Another case closed, my dear Watson.
Morgan, come back. He's stuck in a loop.
For I was blind but now I see.
The cat's out of the bag now.
Mr. Bender, about last night,
that was just a misunderstanding.
You didn't understand?
Well, let me explain.
You were having sex with you.
No, you see, a bureaucrat of my rank
isn't supposed to fraternize.
That's what makes it so juicy.
It's a forbidden fruit angle
everybody loves.
First I'll say, "You'll never guess
who saw Fry and Morgan doing it."
And they'll say, "Who, Bender, who?"
And I'll say, "It was lovable old Bender."
- Hey, what did you do to him?
- I downloaded his brain.
Everything that is Bender is right here.
His mind, his memories...
His in-your-face interface.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
But, Bender need brain for smart making.
What did you do now? Stop doing things.
I sent the disk to be filed
at the Central Bureaucracy.
I did what I had to do, Fry.
He was a bad robot.
No, he was a bad friend.
I want him back right now.
Then you should have filed
a request 20 years ago.
Grr! I'm sick of you and your bureaucracy.
Dirty boy!
You and Morgan were having an affair?
I couldn't help it.
She loved me because of the part of me
that's a slob.
I loved her because of the part of me
that's desperate.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
Poor Bender.
Without his brain
he's become all quiet and helpful.
We've got to go to the Central Bureaucracy
and get that disk back.
- Yes, we must.
- Yeah.
Why?
Well, those arguments aside,
we're still going.
You can't just waltz into
the Central Bureaucracy.
It's a tangled web of red tape
and regulations.
I've never been,
but a friend of mine went completely mad
just trying to find the washroom there.
Then we'll need a guide.
Someone who's been there before.
I've been there. Lots of times.
Look at that. The carts go out full,
but they come in empty.
- It's criminally inefficient.
- Quiet, mate.
Pulling the empty carts is
the closest thing we get to sleep.
But don't ya see?
They could increase efficiency 4%
if they used the empty carts
to bring in heavy mining machinery.
Hey, I like the way you think.
Oh, Lord.
You know, you ought to be
a bureaucrat or something.
Man, how long is this going to take?
I'm still waiting on my birth certificate.
Well, it doesn't look like
I'll make it inside with the rest of you.
But good luck. Just leave me where I drop.
Oh, great. Someone had a baby.
Come on. I have a better idea.
Excuse me. We're from
the Planet Express delivery company.
We're here to deliver a robot.
I am Bender.
Please insert girder.
Looks like we've got a new office cutup.
Look out!
I'm going to crash my slow-mobile.
I had to swerve to avoid you.
While you're crashing could you tell us
where all these canisters end up?
Oh, you want Central Filing.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Wonderful.
No!
Central Filing?
Of course I know where that is.
- I'm a Grade 20.
- Where is it?
- I can't tell you. What do I look like?
- A Grade 16?
We're getting nowhere slowly.
Here. I'll address this
to the Central Filing room.
Then we'll track it
with my wrist LoJack-a-mater.
Cold.
Warmer.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
Please don't tell my supervisor
I was sleeping.
This is it. We'll just run in,
grab Bender's disk, and run out. Got it?
We'll never find that disk,
will we, Bender?
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
You're right. Nothing is over
as long as there's one thin ray of hope.
Lost something?
I should have known you'd come here
rather than follow proper procedure.
And I did know,
and that's why I came here.
Listen, Morgan, we're through.
You're an evil, heartless woman
and I never want to see you again.
However, would you help us get Bender back
for old times' sake?
I'm afraid he's lost
in the master in-pile.
And it would take some sort of giant
mechanical atomic-powered
sorting machine to find him.
You rang?
Damn it, Hermes, just jump already.
Stop hogging that healthy liver.
No, I want to live.
Organizing that forced-labor spa
rekindled my lifelong love of Bureaucracy.
My Hermes got that hellhole
running so efficiently
that all the physical labor is now done
by a single Australian man.
But how did you know we were here?
Dr. Zoidberg brought us.
It was me. I'm the hero.
Request for explanation
of incident meeting.
- Number one point zero.
I hereby petition you
for an emergency sort-and-file
under regulation two-point...
Don't quote me regulations.
I co-chaired the committee
that reviewed the recommendation
to revise the color of the book
that regulation's in.
We kept it gray.
Sir, please. I must locate the disk
with my friend's brain on it.
Very well. But your bureaucratic license
will be revoked
if you fail to sort the master in-pile
by closing time.
1:00 p.m.
That's only four minutes from now.
Requisition me a beat.
When I was four there was
A hurricane in Kingston town
With a foot and a half of water
Everyone was all right,
But I cried all night
It blew my alphabet blocks out of order
And they said this boy's born
To be a bureaucrat
Born to be all obsessive and snotty
I made my friends and relations
File long applications
To get into my tenth birthday party
But something changed
When my man turned pro
I was sorting but I wasn't smiling
He forgot that it's not
About badges and ranks
It's supposed to be about the filing
People
We didn't choose to be bureaucrats
No, that's what almighty Jah made us
We'd treat people like swine
And make 'em stand in line
Even if nobody paid us
They say the world looks down
On the bureaucrats
They say we're anal compulsive and weird
But when push comes to shove
You've got to do what you love
Even if it's not a good idea
Zoidberg!
They said I probably
Shouldn't be a surgeon
They pooh-poohed my electric frankfurter
They said I probably
Shouldn't fly with just one eye
I am Bender
Please insert girder
Everybody sing Jamaica
Jamaica
Just the bureaucrats
Just the Grade 19s
Jamaica
Sing me home
When push comes to shove
You've got to do what you love
Even if it's not a good idea
I'm Bender, baby!
Please insert liquor!
- Congratulations.
- Way to go.
Congratulations indeed.
But you finished with two seconds to spare
so I'm demoting you.
A good bureaucrat never finishes early.
That's okay, Hermes.
At least we have you back.
Not yet, you don't.
I'm still acting bureaucrat
of Planet Express
and I have some changes to make.
First, Fry, you're fired. Second...
Not so fast.
While I was sorting
I came upon a certain document
filed by one Morgan Proctor.
Form "B."
Notification of romantic entanglement.
That's right. She fraternized me.
That form isn't about you.
It refers to my high school prom date.
It was a regulation date that ended
in regulation disappointment.
Yes, but you only stamped it four times.
No, no. I was young and reckless.
Bureaucrat Conrad,
you are technically correct.
The best kind of correct.
I hereby promote you to Grade 37.
And as for you. Guards.
Bring me the forms
I need to fill out to have her taken away.
Well, it looks like I'll be needing
my heroic bureaucrat back.
At severely reduced pay, of course.
It's better than nothing.
What about me? Can I come back
at severely reduced pay?
You got it, mon.
In fact, severely reduced pay all around.
Come on, wife. Let's blow this joint.
Now it's time for my song.
When I was two
There was a tidal wave in...
Aw...